connoisseurusveg.com 2018-12-30

# Privacy Policy - Connoisseurus Veg

Your privacy is important. The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to apprise you information that might be collected when you visit Connoisseurus Veg (hereinafter “Website”) and how such information might be used by the Website and Alissa Saenz (hereinafter “the Author”).

This Website may collect, store and use the following kinds of personal information:

(a)                Information about your computer and about your visits to and use of this website including your IP address, geographical location, browser type and version, operating system, referral source, length of visit, page views and website navigation paths.

(b)               E-mail addresses or other information that you provide when subscribing to our Website via email.

(c)                E-mail addresses, your websites, or other information that you provide when commenting on this Website.

(d)               Information concerning your use and interaction with advertisements on this Website, including third party websites visited through advertisements on this Website.

(e)               Purchases made through affiliate links provided on this Website.

(f)                 Any other information that you provide in any way to this Website or the Author.

Any information received from you via the above or in any other way through this Website may be used in the following ways:

(a)               To modify and improve this Website based on user demographics and activity.

(b)              To enable your use of the services available on this Website.

(c)               To correspond with you concerning this Website.

(d)              To send you marketing communications.

(e)              To provide you with information requested via this website, including the distribution of subscription materials.

(f)                To select advertisements based on user demographics and activity.

(g)               To provide third parties with statistical information about this Website’s users.

(h)              To keep this Website secure and prevent fraud.

The Author may disclose your personal information to third parties insofar as reasonably necessary for the purposes set out in this policy, or as required by law, but will not, without your express consent, supply any of your personal information to any third party for purposes of said third party’s direct marketing activities.

The Author agrees to take reasonable precautions to protect your personal information. However, you acknowledge that transmission of information over the internet is inherently insecure, and complete security can never be guaranteed.

This Website uses third-party advertising companies to serve ads and/or collect anonymous information when you visit this Website. These companies may use aggregated information (such as click stream information, browser type, time and date subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over, but not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>. To  
opt-out of this type of advertising, please see: <http://www.aboutads.info/choices>.

This Website includes links to third party websites. Any visit to any such third-party website is done at your own risk and you acknowledge that the Author has no control over the privacy practices and policies of such third party websites.

This Website may use cookies to personalize your experience. You may disable the ability of this Website to use cookies by modifying your web browser. Doing so may have a negative impact on your ability to interact with this Website.

This Privacy Policy may be revised and updated from time to time. The date at which this Privacy Policy was last updated is reflected by the date at the bottom of the page.

If a provision of this Privacy Policy is determined by any court or other competent authority to be unlawful and/or unenforceable, the other provisions will continue in effect.

This Privacy Policy shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the law of the state of Pennsylvania, United States of America. Any disputes arising hereunder shall be resolved by the courts located in the state of Pennsylvania.

Last update May 21, 2015.
